{
    "Basic structure": [
        {
            "question": "How many branching roads does the intersection have?",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many driving lanes does Road 0 have going towards the intersection?",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many driving lanes does Road 0 have going away from the intersection?",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many driving lanes does Road 4 have going towards the intersection?",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many driving lanes does Road 4 have going away from the intersection?",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many driving lanes does Road 3 have going towards the intersection?",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many driving lanes does Road 3 have going away from the intersection?",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many driving lanes does Road 1 have going towards the intersection?",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many driving lanes does Road 1 have going away from the intersection?",
            "answer": "1"
        }
    ],
    "Road relations": [
        {
            "question": "If a vehicle enters from Road 0 then goes straight, what is the ID of the Road it arrives?",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "If a vehicle enters from Road 4 then goes straight, what is the ID of the Road it arrives?",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "If a vehicle enters from Road 3 then goes straight, what is the ID of the Road it arrives?",
            "answer": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "If a vehicle enters from Road 1 then goes straight, what is the ID of the Road it arrives?",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "If a vehicle enters from Road 0 lane 1, is it allowed to turn right?",
            "answer": "No"
        }
    ],
    "Crossing routes": [
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 1, and another vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 0, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 1, and another vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 3, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 1, and another vehicle goes from Road 3 to Road 0, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 1, and another vehicle goes from Road 1 to Road 0, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 1, and another vehicle goes from Road 1 to Road 4, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 1, and another vehicle goes from Road 1 to Road 3, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 4, and another vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 0, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 4, and another vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 1, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 4, and another vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 3, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 4, and another vehicle goes from Road 3 to Road 0, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 4, and another vehicle goes from Road 3 to Road 1, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 3, and another vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 1, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 3, and another vehicle goes from Road 3 to Road 4, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 3, and another vehicle goes from Road 3 to Road 0, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 0 to Road 3, and another vehicle goes from Road 3 to Road 1, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 1, and another vehicle goes from Road 3 to Road 4, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 1, and another vehicle goes from Road 1 to Road 4, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 1, and another vehicle goes from Road 1 to Road 3, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 3, and another vehicle goes from Road 3 to Road 4, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 4 to Road 3, and another vehicle goes from Road 3 to Road 1, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "If one vehicle goes from Road 3 to Road 1, and another vehicle goes from Road 1 to Road 3, will their paths at the intersection cross?",
            "answer": "No"
        }
    ]
}